const quizQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Who is the General Secretary of MLSC?",
    options: ["Tanmay Bhaiya", "Agrim Bhaiya", "Prisha Didi", "Vansh Bhaiya"],
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Whose idea was it to name the media department 'MMS'?",
    options: ["Bill Gates", "Vanika Didi", "Navdeep Bhaiya", "Preksha Didi"],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What does the word 'Supercalifragilisticexpialidocious' mean?",
    options: [
      "Very bad",
      "Exceptionally good",
      "Extremely hot",
      "We just made this up",
    ],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Who is known as the 'Father of the Nation'?",
    options: ["Narendra Modi", "Godse", "Jawaharlal Nehru", "M. K. Gandhi"],
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the current President of India?",
    options: ["Narendra Modi", "Donald Trump", "Droupadi Murmu", "Salman Khan"],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the cartoon, very popular among Gen Z, that has a camera as the main antagonist?",
    options: [
      "Rizzeler Camera",
      "Skibidi Toilet",
      "Attack on Titan",
      "Shin-Chan",
    ],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the primary function of a servo motor in robotics projects?",
    options: [
      "To measure temperature",
      "To provide precise angular movement",
      "To generate ultrasonic signals",
      "To detect obstacles",
    ],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Interstellar*, what is the name of the robot that accompanies Cooper and his crew on their mission?",
    options: ["HAL", "TARS", "WALL-E", "EVA"],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the symbolic meaning of the green light in *The Great Gatsby*?",
    options: [
      "Hope and dreams",
      "Wealth and status",
      "Love and betrayal",
      "Freedom and power",
    ],
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Dead Poets Society*, what phrase does Mr. Keating use to inspire his students to seize the day?",
    options: ["Carpe diem", "Veni, vidi, vici", "Memento mori", "Ad astra"],
    answer: 0,
  },
];
